A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Fellowships and Training Programs, RG 4 FA1402
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Training Programs, 1971-2005; 4
  - Indo-American Fellowship Program (IAFP), 1976-1995; 2
    - IAFP, LT, Wolfe, Linda D., NSF, 1987-1988 (Box 390, Folder 9)
    - IAFP, General Information, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 10)
    - IAFP, LT, Barnhill, James O., S, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 11)
    - IAFP Selection Committee Meeting, 1987 October 9 (Box 390, Folder 12)
    - IAFP, Standard Letters, Allowances and Forms (Box 390, Folder 13)
    - IAFP, LT, Burton, Thomas, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 14)
    - IAFP, LT, De Voe, Dorsh Marie, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 15)
    - IAFP, LT, Engel, Peter, S, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 16)
    - IAFP, LT, Fisher, Nora, S, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 17)
    - IAFP, LT, George, Robert, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 18)
    - IAFP, LT, Saunders, Wade, S, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 19)
    - IAFP, LT, Varma, Arvind, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 20)
    - IAFP, LT, Newberry, James, S, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 21)
    - IAFP, LT, Perry, John, S, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 22)
    - IAFP, LT, Sharp, Loretta M., S, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 23)
    - IAFP, LT, Ubbelohde, Mary, S, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 24)
    - IAFP, LT, Alternates, 1988-1989 (Box 390, Folder 25)
    - IAFP, ST, Herman-Rosenberg, Yvonne, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 391, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, ST, Kau, Ka-Sing, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 391, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, ST, Lerman, Ora, S, 1988-1989 (Box 391, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, ST, Harring, Sidney, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 391, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, ST, Nolan, Mary, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 391, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, ST, Shepard, Paul Howe, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 391, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, ST, Pinnault, David, S, 1988-1989 (Box 391, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, ST, Ruback, Richard B., NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 391, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, ST, Evans, Peter, NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 391, Folder 9)
    - IAFP, General Correspondence & Telexes (Box 391, Folder 10)
    - IAFP, Tax Information, Grantees and Sub-Commission Exchanges (Box 391, Folder 11)
    - IAFP, ST, Lust, Barbara, NSF, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 12)
    - IAFP, ST, Norton, Anne, NSF, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 13)
    - IAFP, ST, West, Douglas, NSF, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 14)
    - IAFP, ST, Wujek, Daniel, NSF, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 15)
    - IAFP, LT, Britton, Barbara, NSF, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 16)
    - IAFP, LT, Kurtz, Lester, NSF, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 17)
    - IAFP, LT, Weiss, Richard, NSF, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 18)
    - IAFP, LT, Chappell, Robert, S, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 19)
    - IAFP, LT, Higby, Sha Sha, S, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 20)
    - IAFP, LT, Ginzel, Andrew & Kristin Jones, S, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 21)
    - IAFP, LT, Leopold, Susan, S, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 22)
    - IAFP, LT, Simon, Maurya, S, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 23)
    - IAFP, LT, Schumacher, Martha Ann, S, 1989-1990 (Box 391, Folder 24)
    - IAFP, General Information, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, LT, Breuer, Lee, S, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, LT, Garfield, Jay, S, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, LT, Sharp, Loretta, S, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, LT, Lerner, Marilyn, S, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, LT, Williams, J. Carol, S, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, ST, White, James P., S, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, ST, Davis, Virginia, S, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, LT, Bond, Charles, NSF, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 9)
    - IAFP, LT, Hoobler, Raymond, NSF, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 10)
    - IAFP, LT, Zoebel, Donald, NSF, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 11)
    - IAFP, LT, Bechtel, Bethany, NSF, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 12)
    - IAFP, ST, Crawford, Michael, NSF, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 13)
    - IAFP, ST, Faas, Richard, NSF, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 14)
    - IAFP, ST Alt, Hansel, Bettina, NSF, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 15)
    - IAFP, ST, Wells, Harrington, NSF, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 16)
    - IAFP, ST, Kennedy, Dane, S, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 17)
    - IAFP, ST, Latkin, Carl, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 18)
    - IAFP, LT, Nabakov, Peter, SI, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 19)
    - IAFP, ST, Whiting, Robert Van, NSF, 1990-1991 (Box 354, Folder 20)
    - IAFP, General File, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 21)
    - IAFP, LT, Amato, Paul, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 22)
    - IAFP, LT, Armijo, Leslie, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 23)
    - IAFP, LT, Ditz, Daryl, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 24)
    - IAFP, LT, Bookstein, Abraham, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 25)
    - IAFP, LT, Berman, Arnold, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 26)
    - IAFP, LT, Buchen, Mary, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 27)
    - IAFP, LT, Buchen, William, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 28)
    - IAFP, LT, Smith, Paul, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 29)
    - IAFP, ST, Foley, Dolores, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 30)
    - IAFP, ST, Jacobson, David, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 31)
    - IAFP, ST, Smith, Bruce, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 354, Folder 32)
    - IAFP, ST, Erstling, Jay, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, LT, Cincotta, Richard, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, ST, Payne, Margaret, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, ST, Hand, Jacqueline, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, ST, Bullard, Beth, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, ST, McDannel, M. Colleen, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, ST, Nute, Peter, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, ST, Ried, Jeffery, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, LT, Shores, Robin, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 9)
    - IAFP, ST, Varel, Vincent, NSF, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 10)
    - IAFP, ST, Slaughter, Neil, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 11)
    - IAFP, ST, Rivers, Victoria, SI, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 12)
    - IAFP, General File, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 13)
    - IAFP, ST, Bowman, John, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 14)
    - IAFP, LT, Lillywhite, Harvey, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 15)
    - IAFP, ST, Lynch, Beverly, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 16)
    - IAFP, LT, Sky, Alison, S, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 17)
    - IAFP, ST, McNamara, Robert, SI, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 18)
    - IAFP, ST, Foster, David, S, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 19)
    - IAFP, ST, Demerath, Nicholas, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 20)
    - IAFP, ST, Trindle, Carl, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 21)
    - IAFP, LT, Webster, Cynthia, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 22)
    - IAFP, ST, Leonetti, Donna, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 23)
    - IAFP, LT, Figueira, Dorothy, S, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 24)
    - IAFP, ST, Goldsmith, Arthur, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 25)
    - IAFP, ST, Marsh, David, S, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 26)
    - IAFP, ST, Parrotta, John, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 27)
    - IAFP, ST, Sherrad, Joseph, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 28)
    - IAFP, ST, Rothenberg, Barbara, S, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 29)
    - IAFP, ST, Peebles, Patrick, S, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 30)
    - IAFP, LT, Rothrarb, Ed, S, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 31)
    - IAFP, ST, Carlton, Charles, S, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 32)
    - IAFP, LT, Rabinovitz, Abby, S, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 33)
    - IAFP, LT, Callahan, Maureen, NSF, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 34)
    - IAFP, General Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 355, Folder 35)
    - IAFP, LT, Grady, Michael, NSF, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, LT, Anderson, Richard, NSF, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, LT, Lang, Gretchen, NSF, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, LT, Reissman, Catherine, NSF, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, LT, Parker, Dorothy, NSF, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, LT, Walters, Linda, NSF, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, ST, Haidt, Jonathan, NSF, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, ST, Nafziger, Estel, NSF, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, LT, Sonntag, Selma, NSF, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 9)
    - IAFP, LT, Goldberg, Jane, SI, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 10)
    - IAFP, LT, Powell, William, SI, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 11)
    - IAFP, LT, Kokler, Andrew, SI, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 12)
    - IAFP, ST, Summers, Carol, SI, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 13)
    - IAFP, ST, Kalamaras, George, SI, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 14)
    - IAFP, LT, Jones, Julie, SI, 1993-1994 (Box 356, Folder 15)
    - IAFP, Nomination Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 16)
    - IAFP, LT, Michie, Barry H., NSF, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 17)
    - IAFP, Meneses, Eloise, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 18)
    - IAFP, ST, Grearson, Jessie C., SI, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 19)
    - IAFP, ST, Lepore, Stephen J., NSF, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 20)
    - IAFP, LT, Mellencamp, Patricia, SI, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 21)
    - IAFP, LT, Bhattacharyya, Deborah, NSF, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 22)
    - IAFP, ST, Levine, Michael P., SI, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 23)
    - IAFP, ST, Michel, Karen, SI, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 24)
    - IAFP, ST, Williams, Stephan R., SI, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 25)
    - IAFP, ST, Burton, Sigrid A., SI, 1994-1995 (Box 356, Folder 26)
  - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), 1987-1998; 3
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Suanda, I Wayan, 1987-1988; 1991-1992 (Box 356, Folder 27)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Basrul, Akram, 1987-1990 (Box 357, Folder 1)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Gagi, Soepono, 1987-1988-1991 (Box 357, Folder 2)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), General, DD-8784 (84)R, 1987-1988 (Box 357, Folder 3)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), General Grant File, DD-8786(84)R, 1987-1988 (Box 357, Folder 4)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Rockefeller Donation, Grant Payments, DD-8991(256), 1989-1990 (Box 357, Folder 5)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), General Grant File, Yayasan-Ford, DD-8920(250), 1989-1990 (Box 357, Folder 6)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Kartiwa, Suwati, 1990 (Box 357, Folder 7)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Coordination and Planning, Rockefeller Foundation, DD-88119(81)R (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Razak, Muhammadin, 1988-1990 (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Pramono, Arifin, 1988-1989 (Box 358, Folder 3)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Himawan, 1988-1990-1992 (Box 358, Folder 4)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Luthfi, Asirato, 1990-1991 (Box 358, Folder 5)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Rijoly, Frans, 1990-1991 (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Wibisono, Pusitasari, 1990-1991 (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP), Yayasan-Ford, DD-90114(324) (Box 359, Folder 3)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 359, Folder 4)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 359, Folder 5)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 359, Folder 6)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Yayasan Nusantara Jaya, 1989 (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Yayasan Nusantara Jaya, 1988 (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Yayasan Nusantara Jaya, 1987 (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Smithsonian Institute, 1987-1989 (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Ford Foundation, 1987-1989 (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - IMTP, Correspondence, Grant Proposal for 1989-1990 to Rockefeller Foundation (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - IMTP Fund Raising, 1987-1988 (Box 360, Folder 7)
    - IMTP Original Program Mailing for ML (Maureen Liebl) (Box 360, Folder 8)
    - IMTP, Correspondence, IMDP (Box 360, Folder 9)
    - IMTP Final Report, 1992 April 3 (Box 360, Folder 10)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 360, Folder 11)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 360, Folder 12)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 360, Folder 13)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Yayasan Nusantara Jaya, 1991-1992 (Box 360, Folder 14-15)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Yayasan Nusantara Jaya, 1990 (Box 360, Folder 16)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Ford Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Ford Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - IMTP, Correspondence, Meg, CCS, 1992-1993 (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Ford Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Yayasan Nusantara Jaya, 1993-1994 (Box 361, Folder 5)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 361, Folder 6)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Yayasan Nusantara Jaya, 1995-1996 (Box 361, Folder 7)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Ford Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 361, Folder 8)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 361, Folder 9)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Ford Foundation, 1997 (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Yayasan Nusantara Jaya, 1997 (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1997 (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Ford Foundation, 1998 (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - IMTP, Correspondence with Yayasan Nusantara Jaya, 1998 (Box 362, Folder 5)
    - IMTP, General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 362, Folder 6)
  - Japan-United States Museum Professional Exchange Program (JUMP), 1995-1999; 4
    - JUMP, Japan-US Museum Professional Exchange Program, General Correspondence, 1999 (Box 362, Folder 7)
    - JUMP, Japan-US Museum Professional Exchange Program, General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 362, Folder 8)
    - JUMP, Japan-US Museum Professional Exchange Program, General Correspondence, 1997 March-December (Box 363, Folder 1)
    - JUMP, Japan-US Museum Professional Exchange Program, General Correspondence, 1997 January-February (Box 363, Folder 2)
    - JUMP, Japan-US Museum Professional Exchange Program, General Correspondence, 1995 October-1996 (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - JUMP, Japan-US Museum Professional Exchange Program, Trip to Japan, Oversized, 1997 April (Box 363, Folder 4)
  - Triangle Arts Program (TAP I), 5
    - Triangle Arts Program (TAP) (Box 364, Folder 1-2)
  - Japan-United States Arts Program (JUSAP), 1971-2005; 6
    - Japanese Grantee, Cai, Guo Qiang, Painting-Sculpture, 1995 (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - Japanese Grantee, Kanai, Yoshiko, PS-1, 1993 (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Grantee, Sakurai, Makiko, Music, 1993 (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - Japanese Grantee, Shirai, Mio, Visual Art, 1993 (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - Japanese Grantee, Fusuhashi, Teiji, Media & Theater, 1993 (Box 365, Folder 5)
    - Japanese Grantee, Tsuda, Yoshinori, Visual Art, 1993 (Box 365, Folder 6)
    - Japanese Grantee, Yamada, Setsuko, Dance, 1993 (Box 365, Folder 7)
    - Japanese Grantee, Nakamoto, Tomoko, Crafts, 1994 (Box 365, Folder 8)
    - Japanese Grantee, Kunimatsu, Asuka, Art Education, 1993 (Box 365, Folder 9)
    - Japanese Grantee, Ishida, Kazushi, Music, 1994 (Box 365, Folder 10)
    - Japanese Grantee, Yoneya, Naoko, General Culture, 1994 (Box 365, Folder 11)
    - Japanese Grantee, Murakami, Takashi, Painting-Sculpture, PS-1, 1994 (Box 365, Folder 12)
    - Japanese Grantee, Ushijima, Tatsuji, Painting-Sculpture, 1994 (Box 365, Folder 13)
    - Japanese Grantee, Matsuo, Megumi, Painting-Sculpture, 1994 (Box 365, Folder 14)
    - Japanese Grantee, Yomogizawa, Shoko, Painting-Sculpture, 1994 (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - Japanese Grantee, Makino, Nozomi, Theater, 1995 (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Grantee, Taniguchi, Gaho, Painting-Sculpture, 1995 (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - Japanese Grantee, Tsuchitori, Toshiyuki, Music, 1995 (Box 366, Folder 4)
    - Japanese Grantee, Koike, Hiroshi, Theater, 1994 (Box 366, Folder 5)
    - Japanese Grantee, Ito, Makoto, Triangle Artists? Workshop, 1993 (Box 366, Folder 6)
    - US Grantee, Friedman, Martin, Museology, 1995 (Box 366, Folder 7-8)
    - US Grantee, Fast Forward, Music, 1995 (Box 366, Folder 9)
    - US Grantee, Nicholas, Donna, Crafts, 1995 (Box 366, Folder 10)
    - US Grantee, Garland, Peter, Music, 1993 (Box 366, Folder 11)
    - US Grantee, Fitch, Douglas, 1993 (Box 367, Folder 1)
    - US Grantee, Kim, Jun Hi, Music, 1993 (Box 367, Folder 2)
    - US Grantee, Rolnick, Neil, Music, 1994 (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - US Grantee, Greenberg, Aimee, Theater, 1994 (Box 367, Folder 4)
    - US Grantee, Bubriski, Kevin, Cinema-Photography, 1994 (Box 367, Folder 5)
    - US Grantee, Heartney, Eleanor, Art History, 1995 (Box 367, Folder 6)
    - US Grantee, Fetscher, Suzanne, 1994 (Box 367, Folder 7)
    - US Grantee, Coates, George, Theater, 1994 (Box 367, Folder 8)
    - US Grantee, Farver, Jane, Museology, 1994 (Box 367, Folder 9)
    - US Grantee, Treib, Marc, Architecture, 1994 (Box 367, Folder 10)
    - US Grantee, Adler, Steven, Theater, 1993 (Box 367, Folder 11)
    - US Grantee, Celli, Joseph, Music, 1993 (Box 367, Folder 12)
    - US Grantee, de Melo, Jacques, Photography, 1993 (Box 367, Folder 13)
    - ACC - Japan-US Arts Program (JUSAP), 1983-1987 (Box 368, Folder 1-2)
    - US Grant, Smith, Leo, 1992 (Box 368, Folder 3)
    - US, Franklin, Joseph, Music Producer, 1992 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - US, Coyne, Petah, VA, 1992 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - US, King, John, Music, 1992 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - US, Boyle, Wickham, Theater, 1992 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - US, Breslin, Lynne, Doris M. Srimarasam, Laura Trippi, 1992 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - 1992 Japanese Grantees (Box 369, Folder 2)
    - Japan-US Arts Program, Declinations, 1990 Spring (Box 370, Folder 1)
    - Japan-US Arts Program, Declinations, 1989 Spring (Box 370, Folder 2)
    - JUSAP, Japan-U.S. Arts Program, Declinations, 1999 (Box 371, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, Japan-U.S. Arts Program, Declinations, 2000 Spring (Box 371, Folder 2)
    - JUSAP, Tokyo, Declinations, 2001 (Box 372, Folder 1-2)
    - Japan-US Arts Program (JUSAP), Declinations, 2000 (Box 373, Folder 1-3)
    - Tokyo, Declinations, Spring Meeting, 2003 (Box 373, Folder 4)
    - Tokyo, Declinations, Spring Meeting, 2003 (Box 374, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, Tokyo, Declinations, 2004 (Box 374, Folder 2)
    - Tokyo, Declinations, 2005 (Box 375, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Declinations, 1988 Spring (Box 375, Folder 2)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Declinations, 1987 Spring (Box 375, Folder 3)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Declinations, 1987 Fall (Box 375, Folder 4)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Applications Received in Tokyo for Consideration, 1986 Spring (Box 376, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Applications Received in Tokyo for Consideration, 1986 October (Box 376, Folder 2)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Declinations, 1985 (Box 376, Folder 3)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Correspondence with Yoko Meada & Richard Emmert, 1988 (Box 376, Folder 4)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 376, Folder 5)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 376, Folder 6)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Correspondence, Yoko Meada & Richard Emmert, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Grantees, Correspondence with Richard Emmert and Others, 1986 (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program-Seibu Museum of Art, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Grantees, Correspondence with Bert Winther and Others, 1985 (Box 377, Folder 4)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program-Seibu Museum of Art, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program, Grantees, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 377, Folder 6)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program-Seibu Museum of Art, Correspondence, 1971-1983 (Box 377, Folder 7)
    - JUSAP, Japan-US Arts Program-Seibu Museum of Art, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 377, Folder 8)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1991 January-May (Box 378, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1991 June-December (Box 378, Folder 2)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1992 January-June (Box 378, Folder 3)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1992 July-December (Box 379, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1993 (Box 379, Folder 2)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1994 (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - Japan-United States Arts Program, Declinations, 1991 Spring (Box 381, Folder 1)
    - Japan-United States Arts Program, Declinations, 1992 Spring (Box 381, Folder 2)
    - Japan-United States Arts Program, Declinations, 1993 Spring (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - Japan-United States Arts Program, Declinations, 1994 Spring (Box 383, Folder 1)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Out of Program, 1, 1984 Autumn; 1985 Spring (Box 384, Folder 1)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Out of Program, 2, 1985 Autumn. 1986 Spring; 1986 Autumn (Box 384, Folder 2)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Out of Program, 3, 1986 Autumn; 1987 Spring (Box 384, Folder 3)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Out of Program, 4, 1987 Spring; Autumn (Box 384, Folder 4)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Out of Program, 5, 1987 Spring-1988 Spring (Box 384, Folder 5)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Out of Program, 6, 1988 Spring-1989 Spring (Box 385, Folder 1)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Out of Program, 7, 1989 Spring (Box 385, Folder 2)
    - (untitled) ACC-JUSAP, Out of Program, 8 (Box 385, Folder 3)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Granted, 5, 1987 Spring; Autumn (Box 385, Folder 4)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Granted, 6, 1988 Spring (Box 386, Folder 1)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Granted, 7, 1989 Spring (Box 386, Folder 2)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Granted, 8, 1989 Autumn-1990 (Box 386, Folder 3)
    - ACC-JUSAP, Granted, 9, 1990 (Box 386, Folder 4)
    - JUSAP, Declinations, 1995 Spring (Box 387, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, Declinations, 1996 Spring (Box 387, Folder 2)
    - JUSAP, Declinations, 1997 Spring (Box 387, Folder 3)
    - JUSAP, Declinations, 1998 (Box 388, Folder 1-2)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 392, Folder 1)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1997 (Box 392, Folder 2)
    - JUSAP, General Correspondence, 1996 (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - Asian Fellowships, 7
    - Asian Fellowships, EC-7022, EC-7131, General Culture-Asia, B-7216, B-7301, B-7401, B-7495, B-7502, B-7602, B-7702 (Box 402, Folder 1)
  - Philippines Fellows, 2001-2002; 8
    - Philippines Fellowship, Capino, Jose, 2001 (Box 393, Folder 1)
    - Philippines Fellowship, Museo Pambata Foundation, 2001 (Box 393, Folder 2)
    - Philippines Fellowship, Villafranca, Ethel, 2001 (Box 393, Folder 3)
    - Philippines Fellowship, Marasigan, Irma A., 2002 (Box 393, Folder 4)
    - Philippines Fellowship, Pastrano, Mozart, 2002 (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Taipei Fellows, 1993-2003; 9
    - Taipei, Declinations, 1996 Spring (Box 394, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations, 1997 Spring (Box 394, Folder 3)
    - Taipei, Declinations, L-Y, 1997 Spring (Box 395, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations, 1998 Spring (Box 395, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations, 1999 Spring (Box 396, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Chuo, Ming-Yu, Music 1, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Chang, Chun-Yien, Music 2, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Yang, Hsiu-Ju, Dance 1, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Wang, Wei-Ming, Dance 2, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Taipei Arts International Association, Dance 3, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Chin, Su Feng, Theatre 2, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Hung, Wei-Ting, Theatre 3, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Kuo, Chen Ti, Movie 1, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Tseng, Te-Shun, Movie 4, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)